A Guide to the Mutual Assurance Society of Virginia Declarations and Revaluations of Assurance, 1796-1966
Library of Virginia
- Mutual Assurance Society of Virginia Declarations and Revaluations of Assurance, 1796-1966.
  - Volume 228 [Declarations 48501-48800],1949. (Volume v228)
  - Volume 229 [Declarations 48801-49100],1950. (Volume v229)
  - Volume 230 [Declarations 49101-49400],1950. (Volume v230)
  - Volume 231 [Declarations 49401-49700],1951. (Volume v231)
  - Volume 232 [Declarations 49701-50000],1951. (Volume v232)
  - Volume 233 [Declarations 50001-50300],1951. (Volume v233)
  - Volume 234 [Declarations 50301-50600],1951. (Volume v234)
  - Volume 235 [Declarations 50601-50900],1952. (Volume v235)
  - Volume 236 [Declarations 50901-51200],1952. (Volume v236)
  - Volume 237 [Declarations 51201-51500],1953. (Volume v237)
  - Volume 238 [Declarations 51501-51800],1953. (Volume v238)
  - Volume 239 [Declarations 51801-52100],1954. (Volume v239)
  - Volume 240 [Declarations 52101-52400],1955. (Volume v240)
  - Volume 241 [Declarations 52401-52700],1956. (Volume v241)
  - Volume 242 [Declarations 52701-53000],1956. (Volume v242)
  - Volume 243 [Declarations 53001-53300],1956. (Volume v243)
  - Volume 244 [Declarations 53301-53600],1957. (Volume v244)
  - Volume 245 [Declarations 53601-53900],1957. (Volume v245)
  - Volume 246 [Declarations 53901-54200],1957. (Volume v246)
  - Volume 247 [Declarations 54201-54500],1958. (Volume v247)
  - Volume 248 [Declarations 54501-54800],1958. (Volume v248)
  - Volume 249 [Declarations 54801-55100],1959. (Volume v249)
  - Volume 250 [Declarations 55101-55400],1959. (Volume v250)
  - Volume 251 [Declarations 55401-55700],1960. (Volume v251)
  - Volume 252 [Declarations 55701-56000],1960. (Volume v252)
  - Volume 253 [Declarations 56001-56300],1961. (Volume v253)
  - Volume 254 [Declarations 56301-56600],1961. (Volume v254)
  - Volume 255 [Declarations 56601-56900],1962. (Volume v255)
  - Volume 256 [Declarations 56901-57200],1963. (Volume v256)
  - Volume 257 [Declarations 57201-57500],1963. (Volume v257)
  - Volume 258 [Declarations 57501-57800],1964. (Volume v258)
  - Volume 259 [Declarations 57801-58100],1965. (Volume v259)
  - Loose policies, 127-13988 and 60A-889A (misc. range),1796-1844, 1846-1862. (Box b45)
  - Loose policies, 14026-21560 (misc. range),1845-1865. (Box b46)
  - Policy book,1796-1803. (Box b47)
  - Policy book for goods and implements,1798-1803. (Box b48)
  - Index to declarations,1796-1821. (Box b49)
  - Index to declarations,1796-1821 (Positive photostatic copy of item in Box b49) (Volume v260)
  - Index to unidentified volumes. (Box b50)
  - Index cards. (Box b51)
  - Property names. (Volume v261)
  - Sanborn fire insurance maps, Alexandria,1931. (Volume v262)
  - Sanborn fire insurance maps, Charlottesville,1929-1959. (Volume v263)
  - Sanborn fire insurance maps, Danville,1920-1951. (Volume v264)
  - Sanborn fire insurance maps, Fredericksburg,1927. (Volume v265)
  - Sanborn fire insurance maps, Harrisonburg, Leesburg, Smithfield, Warrenton,1907-1926. (Box b052)
  - Sanborn fire insurance maps, Lexington,1930. (Volume v266)
  - Sanborn fire insurance maps, Lynchburg,1907-1953. (Volume v267)
  - Sanborn fire insurance maps, Norfolk Vol. 1,1928-1956. (Volume v268)
  - Sanborn fire insurance maps, Norfolk Vol. 2,1928-1961. (Volume v269)
  - Sanborn fire insurance maps, Norfolk Vol. 3,1928-1961. (Volume v270)
  - Sanborn fire insurance maps, Norfolk Vol. 5,1928-1960. (Volume v271)
  - Sanborn fire insurance maps, Petersburg,1915-1955. (Volume v272)
  - Sanborn fire insurance maps, Portsmouth Vol. 1,1920-1957. (Volume v273)
  - Sanborn fire insurance maps, Portsmouth Vol. 2,1920-1957. (Volume v274)
  - Sanborn fire insurance maps, Richmond Vol. 1,1952. (Volume v275)
  - Sanborn fire insurance maps, Richmond Vol. 2,1952. (Volume v276)
  - Sanborn fire insurance maps, Richmond Vol. 3,1952. (Volume v277)
  - Sanborn fire insurance maps, Richmond Vol. 4,1952. (Volume v278)
  - Sanborn fire insurance maps, Richmond Vol. 5,1952. (Volume v279)
  - Sanborn fire insurance maps, Roanoke,1919-1953. (Volume v280)
  - Sanborn fire insurance maps, South Richmond,1952. (Volume v281)
  - Sanborn fire insurance maps, Staunton,1929. (Volume v282)
  - Sanborn fire insurance maps, Suffolk Vol. 1,1920. (Volume v283)
  - Sanborn fire insurance maps, Suffolk Vol. 2,1926-1960. (Volume v284)
  - Sanborn fire insurance maps, Williamsburg,1933. (Volume v285)
  - Sanborn fire insurance maps, Winchester,1927. (Volume v286)
  - Sanborn map index, Norfolk, 1944-1956. (Volume v287)
  - Sanborn map index, Norfolk, 1961-1964. (Volume v288)
  - Sanborn map index, Richmond, 1952-1968. (Volume v289)
  - Sanborn maps, Description and utilization of. (Volume v290)